哦 哦 哦
Ooh, ooh, ooh.
丑裸男在装饰圣诞树
Ugly Naked Guy is decorating his tree.
天啊 你们该来看看他的圣诞球有多大
Oh, my God, you should see the size of his Christmas balls!
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
你们要给管理员小费多少钱？
How much did you tip the super?
对 我们想给他五十块 但我们不想太丢脸
Yeah, we were gonna give 50, but we don't wanna look bad.
今年我们只送他饼干
Oh, this year we just made him cookies.
那么给25块就够了
And 25 it is.
你们送他饼干？
Heh. You gave him cookies?
- 给钱太冷漠了   - 对
- Money is so impersonal.     - Yeah.
饼干可以表达关切之意
Cookies says someone really cares.
好吧 我们破产了 但送饼干真的有那样的意义
All right, we're broke, but cookies do say that.
我了解
I can see that.
一盘布朗宁饼干会让我想起打油诗
A plate of brownies told me a limerick.
菲比 我得问你一件事 这是好笑的布朗宁饼干吗？
Pheebs, let me ask you something. Were these, uh, "funny" brownies?
不是特别好笑
Not especially.
但我想他们加了大麻
But, you know, I think they had pot in them.
各位 你们还送谁饼干当做小费？
So, you guys, who else did you tip with cookies?
邮差 管理员
Uh, the mailman, the super...
送报生
Oh, and the newspaper delivery guy.
天啊
Oh, my God.
什么？
What?
我想你们不会喜欢这个
Uh, I don't think you're gonna like this.
噢 哇噢
Oh, wow.
天啊
Oh, gosh.
这是包在体育版里被弄碎的饼干
Oh, these are cookies smashed in the Sports section.
他还玩了我的字谜游戏
And he did my crossword puzzle.
对 他答错了 除非横14的"盖西文音乐剧"
Yeah, but not very well, unless 14 across, "Gershwin musical"...
正确答案是"去死吧…"
actually is "Bite me, bite me, bite me."
没有人告诉你活着有多累
∮ So no one told you life was gonna be this way ∮
上班受罪 口袋空空 爱情变累赘
∮ Your job's a joke, you're broke, your love life's D.O.A. ∮
寂寞又潦倒 受气又受累
∮ It's like you're always stuck in second gear ∮
日复一日 年复一年
∮ When it hasn't been your day, ∮
时运不济 活着受罪
∮ your week, your month, or even your year ∮
你我永不离弃
∮ but I'll be there for you ∮
纵有狂风暴雨
∮ When the rain starts to pour ∮
你我永不离弃
∮ I'll be there for you ∮
支持一如往昔
∮ Like I've been there before ∮
你我永不离弃
∮ I'll be there for you ∮
你我相偎相依
∮ 'Cause you're there for me too ∮
我不敢相信圣诞节已经到了 你们知道吗？
I can't believe it's Christmas already. You know?
前一天你还在吃火鸡 隔一天
One day you're eating turkey, the next thing you know...
天神在跳舞 鹅下在蛋
your lords are a-leaping and your geese are a-laying. Heh.
所以每年这个时候 鹅都很轻松
Which is why geese are so relaxed this time of year.
- 大家好   - 嘿
- Hey, guys.     - Hey.
嘿 瑞秋
Hey, Rach.
我帮你买了礼物
I, uh, got you a little present.
我来帮你拆开
I'll open it.
这是弹簧圈
It's a Slinky!
记得吗？
Ha, ha. Remember, huh?
滚下楼 不论一个或两个
Walks downstairs Alone or in pairs
大家都知道它是…
Everyone knows it's...
一个大弹簧
Just a big spring.
你还在气我 因为…
You're still mad because of the whole...
你不想跟我在一起的理由清单？
Horrible list of reasons not to be with me?
我们何不叫它是不幸的意外？
How about we just call it "the unfortunate incident"?
阿甘 你住的地方有楼梯吗？
Hey, Gunther. You got stairs in your place?
- 有啊   - 给你玩吧
- Yeah.     - Go nuts.
- 大家好   - 嘿
- Hey, guys.     - Hey.
袋子里是什么东西？
What's in the bag?
只是一些礼物
Mm, just some presents.
来吧 让我们看看你买了什么
Come on, show us what you bought.
你知道你想要给我们看
You know you want to.
好吧
Okay.
这是小班送我爸妈的相框
This is a picture frame from Ben to my parents.
真的好可爱
Oh, that's cute.
这是送给苏珊及卡萝的女女毛巾
Some "Hers" and "Hers" towels for Susan and Carol.
我买了这件上衣送给妈
And, uh, I got this blouse for Mom.
- 罗斯 那真的好漂亮   - 是吗？
- Ross, that is gorgeous!     - Yeah?
看看这些逼真的假勋章
Look at these authentic fake medals!
妈会拿到最佳服装奖
Mom's gonna be voted "best dressed"...
在假军校里
at the make-believe military academy!
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
- 圣诞夜快乐   - 你也是
- Happy Christmas Eve Eve.     - You too.
天啊 你在哪里买的？
Oh, my God! Where did you get this?
梅西百货三楼的家饰部
Uh, Macy's, third floor, home furnishings.
他是我爸
This is my father!
这是我爸的照片
This is a picture of my dad!
菲比 那是相框里原来就有的照片
Uh, Pheebs, that's the guy that comes in the frame.
不 他是我爸 我可以证明
No, it's my dad. I'll show you.
菲比 我以为你爸在坐牢
I thought your dad was in prison.
不 他是我继父
No, that's my stepdad.
我生父在我出生前就抛弃了我们
My real dad's the one that ran out on us before I was born.
为什么你上不了欧普拉的节目？
How have you never been on Oprah?
看吧 就是他
Look, see? This is him.
我妈死前给了我他的照片 是同一个人
My mother gave me this picture before she died. Same guy!
甜心 这是相框原有的照片
Honey, uh, this is a picture of the frame guy...
那个男的牵着柯利牧羊犬 在蓝幕前面拍照
posing in front of a blue screen with a collie.
那不是蓝慕 那是…
It's not a blue screen. It's just...
或许那天的天气很好
Maybe it was just really clear that day.
好吧 我得跟我外婆谈一谈
Okay, I have to talk to my grandmother.
- 等一下 甜心   - 菲比
- Wait a minute, honey!     - Pheebs.
- 喔   - 哇
- Whoa.     - Wow.
我试着勾引我老板的前妻跟我上床
I'm trying to get my boss's ex-wife to sleep with me.
乔伊
Joey.
菲比有问题时 大家都愿意听
Oh, but when Phoebe has a problem, everyone's all ears!
顿艾瑟林文斯
Esther Livingston.
死了
Gone!
嘿 小菲
Um... Hi, Pooh.
外婆 你在做什么？
Hi, Gram. Ahem, what you doing?
更新电话簿
Oh, just updating the phone book.
外婆
Um, Gram? Um...
我能再看一下我爸的照片吗？
Can I see the pictures of my dad again?
噢
Oh.
没问题
Oh, sure, sure.
怎么了？
Uh... Huh, how come?
我只是想看看他
Just, you know, to see him.
没问题 拿去吧
Oh, sure. Here.
好吧
All right, uh...
这是你爸在草原拍的
This is the one of your father in a meadow.
他在教一个小男生放风筝
And, uh, helping a little boy fly a kite.
这是他参加毕业典礼
And here he is at a graduation.
另一场毕业典礼
Another graduation.
他真的是我爸吗？
Is this really my father?
他真的是你…
Is it really your...?
当然是的
Well, of course it is.
我闻到烟味了 因为有人要火烧屁股了
I smell smoke. Maybe because someone's pants are on fire!
我…
Well, I...
我们当祖孙这么多年
In all the years we've been grandmother and granddaughter...
你从来没说过谎
you've never lied.
好吧 他不是你爸 那是相框原有的照片
All right, that's not your father. It's a picture of a guy in a frame.
天啊
Oh, God.
那是你妈的点子
It was your mother's idea.
她不要你知道你生父是谁
She didn't want you to know your real father...
因为他离开时 她真的很伤心
because it hurt her so much when he left.
我不想配合她
I didn't wanna go along with it.
但她死了 我很难跟她吵
But then she died and it was harder to argue with her.
不是不可能 但真的很难
Not impossible, but harder.
好吧 他不是著名的树医生？
All right. So he's not a famous tree surgeon?
我想他没有住在 没电话的缅甸小屋子里
And I guess he doesn't live in a hut in Burma where there's no phones?
就我所知 他在北部当药剂师
Last I heard, he was a pharmacist somewhere upstate.
那一点道理都没有
That makes no sense.
为什么村民要崇拜一个药剂师？
Why would the villagers worship a pharmacist?
甜心
Honey.
- 对   - 对
- Oh. Yeah.     - Yeah.
总之我只知道那么多
Anyway, that's all I know.
没错
That...
还有这个
and this.
这是…
This...
他真正的长相
is the real him.
噢
Oh.
我记得我爸穿着红衣服
I remember my father all dressed up in the red suit...
黑色大靴子跟合成皮腰带
the big black boots and the patent leather belt...
在楼下躲来躲去的 他不要我们看到他
sneaking around downstairs. He didn't want us to see him...
因为他喝醉了 他撞到东西 把大家都吵醒了
but he'd be drunk, so he'd crash into something and wake everybody up.
那听起来不像是个快乐的耶诞节
That doesn't sound like a very merry Christmas.
谁说那跟圣诞节有关系了？
Who said anything about Christmas?
- 嗨   - 谁有菲比的消息？
- Hi.     - Anyone hear from Phoebe yet?
没有 完全没消息
No, nothing.
我希望她没事
I hope she's okay.
我能了解她的感觉
I know exactly what she's going through.
你怎么会了解她的感觉？
How do you know what she's going through?
她跟我们说了
She told us.
你买了什么 摩妮卡？
What do you got there, Monica?
派对要用的东西
Stuff for the party.
你们应该去血拼不是吗？
Aren't you guys supposed to be shopping?
你们还没有买礼物？
You didn't buy presents yet?
明天是圣诞夜 你们打算怎么办？
Tomorrow's Christmas Eve! What are you gonna do?
黏土动画人物才会那样子说话吧？
Don't you have to be Claymation to say stuff like that?
对了 摩妮卡 我想邮差不喜欢你的饼干
Oh, by the way, Mon, I don't think the mailman liked your cookies.
这是你妈寄来的装饰品
Here are the ornaments your mom sent.
好吧
Well...
或许邮差喜欢饼干 只是我们给他的饼干不够多
Maybe the mailman liked the cookies. We just didn't give him enough.
摩妮卡 连鸽子都比你聪明
Monica, pigeons learn faster than you.
瑞秋
Hey, Rach. Ahem.
我知道怎么做能让你开心一点
I think I know what will make you feel better.
你何不列一张关于我的清单
How about you make a list about me?
算了 我才不要站在这里…
Forget it. I'm not gonna stand here...
列清单
and make a list.
好吧 你爱抱怨
Okay, you're whiny...
你偏执 没有安全感
you are obsessive, you are insecure...
- 非常没胆   - 呃
- you're gutless.     - Heh.
你无法把握当下
You don't ever just seize the day.
你喜欢我一整年 却没采取任何行动
You liked me for a year and you didn't do anything about it.
还有…你擦了太多发胶
And, uh... Oh, you wear too much of that gel in your hair.
看吧 你…
See, there. You, uh...
好吧 你照我的话去做了
All right, you did what I said.
- 你知道吗？ - 嗯？
- And you know what?     - Hmm?
你说的对 我觉得舒坦多了
You're right. I do feel better.
谢谢你 罗斯
Thank you, Ross.
对 在奥巴尼 能告诉我法兰克布非的电话吗？
Yeah, in Albany. Could I have the number of Frank Buffay?
好的 在伊夕卡？
Okay. Um, in lthaca?
好吧 在沙拉托加？
All right, um, Saratoga?
在奥尼昂坦？
Oneonta?
你知道吗？你不该自称是查号台
You know what? You shouldn't call yourself Information!
嘿
Hey.
外婆 如果那是你的真名
Hello, Grandma. If that is, in fact, your real name.
别这样 小菲 你的气还没消？
Come on now, Pooh. Don't still be mad at me.
- 怎么样？ - 没结果
- How's it going?     - Oh, not so good.
北部很大 他很渺小 你自己想吧
Upstate's pretty big. He's pretty small. You do the math.
我想没有他 你能过得更好
Well, I think you're better off without him.
甜心 我知道他是你爸
Oh, honey, I know he's your daddy.
对我来说 他仍是那个不负责的混蛋
But to me, he's still the irresponsible creep...
他把你妈锁起来 偷走她的庭院装饰
who locked up your mom and stole her Gremlin.
我了解 我只想知道他是谁
I know. I just wanted to know who he was, you know?
对 我知道
Yeah, I know.
好吧
Okay.
我没有完全对你坦白 当我跟你说我不知道
I wasn't completely honest with you when I told you that, uh, I didn't know...
他住在哪里
exactly where he lived.
你是什么意思？
What do you mean?
他住在密德镇罗尔路74号
He lives at 74 Laurel Drive in Middletown.
看到乳制品女王 就代表你过头了
If you hit the Dairy Queen, you've gone too far.
你可以开我的计程车去
You can take my cab.
哇
Wow.
谢谢
Thank you.
- 不能让其他人开那辆计程车   - 我知道
- Nobody else drives that cab.     - Uh-huh. Got it.
噢
Oh.
- 我要去见我爸了   - 哈哈
- I'm gonna see my dad!     - Ha-ha-ha.
- 谢谢   - 哈哈
- Thank you.     - Oh. Ha, ha.
好吧
Mm, okay. Oh.
祝我好运吧 外公
Wish me luck, Grandpa.
嘿
Hey.
菲比把计程车开过来了吗？
Phoebe here with the cab yet?
对 她将隐形计程车开过来了
Yeah, she brought the invisible cab.
上车吧
Hop in!
她得快点过来 商店七点就打烊了
She'd better get here. The stores close at 7.
别担心 开车到菲比爸家要两小时
It'll be two hours to Phoebe's dad's house...
他们会见面 聊天 分享人生故事
they'll meet, chat, swap life stories.
我们有的是时间
We'll still have plenty of time.
- 她来了   - 嘿
- Hey, here she comes!     - Hey.
嘿
Hey, hey.
嗨
Hi.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
你们能相信吗？
Can you believe this?
两小时后我就有爸爸了
In like two hours I'm gonna have a dad.
对 非常重大
Yeah, big stuff.
- 好吧 我们出发吧   - 好的
- Okay, let's go.     - Okay.
- 拿去 这个给你   - 好的
- Here, you have to hold this.     - Okay.
"煞车左边 油门右边"？
"Brake, left. Gas, right"?
那是我的作弊小抄
Uh-huh, that's my cheat sheet.
- 我的安全带在哪里？ - 那边没有安全带
- Where's my seat belt?     - That side doesn't have one.
急救人员得把它剪开
The paramedics had to cut through it.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
来吧 快告诉我 拜托
Come on, just tell me. Please, please.
这是第16次 不 我不觉得你偏执
For the 16th time, no, I do not think you're obsessive.
- 天啊 这里真的好热   - 瑞秋 关掉暖气
- Oh, it's hot in here!     - Rach, get the heat.
- 罗斯 拜托你关掉暖气   - 没问题
- Ross, turn the heat down, please?     - Sure.
那是不一样的 偏执和…
There's a difference between obsessive...
罗斯 暖气
Ross, the heat!
好吧 暖气 我算是偏执吗？
Okay. Heat, heat, heat. And I'm the obsessive one?
好的
Okay.
这边是开
This way is on.
所以这边是…
So this is...
关
off.
你把暖气弄坏了？
Did you just break the radiator?
不 我只是转一下开关
No, I was turning the knob and...
就变成这样了
here it is.
把它装回去
Well, put it back!
它…
It, uh...
- 装不回去   - 我得打电话给管理员
- It won't go back.     - Ugh. I'll call the super.
来吧 让我试试看
Here, let me try.
没错 我忘记你有融化金属的超能力
Oh, oh, that's right. I forgot about your ability to fuse metal.
那个笑话很不错
Hey, it's Funny's cousin...
但一点都不好笑
Not Funny!
崔格先生
Hi, Mr. Treeger?
我是住在楼上的瑞秋葛林
It's Rachel Green from upstairs.
对 有人弄坏我们的暖气开关
Yes, somebody, uh, broke our knob on the radiator...
这里真的很热
and it's really hot in here.
对 热到可以烤饼干了
Yes, it's hot enough to bake cookies.
你能在六点前帮我们换新的吗？
Well, do you think we could have a new one by 6?
什么？不 星期二？我们不能等到星期二
What? No, no. Tuesday? We can't wait until Tuesday.
今晚我们要举行派对
We're having a party tonight.
好吧 给他小费
Okay, tip the man.
如果他不喜欢我们的饼干 太可惜了
If he doesn't like our cookies, too bad.
我不会被勒索
I won't be blackmailed.
听着 就算有点热
Look, if it gets a little warm...
我们可以办主题派对
it can be a theme party.
这是派对主题 "请进 感受一下培根的生活"
Here's a theme: "Come on in, live like bacon!"
我们到了
Ooh, this is it.
74号
Seventy-four.
原来这个的功用是那样啊
Oh, so that's what this is for!
哇
Wow.
就是这里 我要见到我爸了
This is it. I'm gonna meet my dad.
这真的很重大对吧？
This is, like, the biggest thing ever, huh?
- 对   - 当然
- Yeah.     - Sure is.
好吧 我要进去了
Here I go. I'm going in.
好的
All right!
祝你好运 菲比
Good luck, Pheebs.
好的
Okay.
我要进去了
Here I go.
我要去了
I'm going.
嗨
Hi.
欢迎光临我们的热带耶诞节派对
Welcome to our tropical Christmas party, heh.
将外套 毛衣 裤子跟衬衫 放到卧室里
Put your coats, sweaters, pants and shirts in the bedroom.
很难看得出来 因为我在流汗
It's hard to tell because I'm sweating...
但我照瓶身说明使用发胶
but I use exactly what the gel bottle says.
约豆子一样的大小 那样怎么会太多呢？
An amount about the size of a pea. How can that be too much?
冰块？
Ice?
冰块 谁要冰块？拿张纸巾
Ice? Ice squares anyone? Take a napkin.
好吧
All right.
摩妮卡
Monica. Monica!
摩妮卡 你的客人变成肉干了
Monica, your guests are turning into jerky.
真的吗？我觉得蛮舒服的
Really? I'm perfectly comfortable.
排队 兄弟 我是下一捆
Ha, ha. Hey! Get in line, buddy. I was next.
崔格先生
Mr. Treeger.
你说你们要办派对
You said there was a party.
对
Oh, yeah.
欢迎光临我们的桑拿屋
Well, hey, welcome to our sauna.
很热吗？我的身体一向都能保持凉爽
Uh, is it hot? My body always stays cool.
或许是因为我的皮很厚
Probably because I have so much skin.
嘿 起司
Hey, cheese!
这是个机会 摩妮卡 给他现金
Here's the chance. Monica, give him cash.
瑞秋 把你的耳环送给他 想想办法 什么都可以
Rachel, give him your earrings. Something. Anything!
不 我不会屈服
No, I will not cave.
我支持摩妮卡
I'm with Mon.
好吧 你说我不懂得把握当下
All right. You know how you say I never seize the day?
虽然他是你们的管理员 我要把握机会
Even though he's your super, I'm seizing.
崔格先生
Mr. Treeger?
这是五十块 圣诞快乐
Here is 50 bucks. Merry Christmas.
噢 哇噢
Oh, wow.
我没帮你准备礼物
I didn't get you anything.
给你五块
Here's five back.
不 那是你的圣诞节小费
No, that's your Christmas tip.
喔 你能顺便修一下暖气吗？
Oh, do you think there's a chance you can fix that radiator now?
不行 我跟女孩们说过
No can do. Like I told the girl...
星期二才能拿到开关零件
I can't get a knob until Tuesday.
- 罗斯   - 什么？
- Ross?     - Yeah?
他在打棒球
He's playing baseball.
你是说他在玩硬的吗？
You mean hardball?
都一样
Whatever.
你要怎么办？
What you gonna do?
对不起 我要把握机会
Excuse me. I'm seizing.
崔格先生
Mr. Treeger?
这是另一张五十块
Here's another 50.
光明节快乐
Happy Hanukkah.
这能帮助你快点拿到开关零件吗？
Will, uh, this help with the knob-getting?
不行
No.
商店星期二才会开门
The place is not open till Tuesday.
我发音有问题吗？
Am I not saying it right?
你真的喜欢我的饼干？
So you really did like my cookies?
对 它们非常有感情 证明你真的关心我
Oh, yeah, they were so personal. It really showed you cared.
你太会把握当下了
Nice seizing...
发胶男孩
gel boy.
好吧
So, uh...
这是槲寄生吗？
Is this, uh, mistletoe?
不 那是…
No, uh, that...
那是罗勒
That is basil.
- 噢   - 耶
- Oh.     - Yeah.
如果那是槲寄生 我可以吻你
If it was mistletoe, I was gonna kiss you.
不 那是罗勒
No, it's still basil.
好吧
Okay.
- 你跑到哪里了？ - 信箱
- How far did you get?     - Mailbox.
- 好吧 我们有进步了   - 嗯哼
- All right, we're getting closer.     - Uh-huh.
菲比 到底发生了什么事？
What's going on?
这真的是一团糟
It's just, like, a whole mess of stuff.
昨天我爸是著名的缅甸树医生
Like yesterday, my dad was this famous Burma tree-surgeon guy.
现在他是药剂师
And, you know, now he's, uh, a pharmacist guy and...
或许他是很酷的药剂师
Well, maybe he's this really cool pharmacist guy.
或许是啊 我要去敲门
Yeah, maybe. And I'll knock on the door...
他会拥抱我 我就有爸爸了
and he'll hug me, and I'll have a dad.
我会去他的药房 大家都会对我好
I'll go to his pharmacy and everyone will be nice to me...
因为我是法兰克的女儿
because, you know, I'm Frank's daughter.
那为什么你不去敲门呢？
So why not go knock?
因为如果他不是个好爸爸呢？
Because, I mean, what if he's not this great dad guy?
如果他还是那个抛弃我妈跟我们的混蛋呢？
What if he's still the dirtbag who ran out on my mom and us?
- 对   - 嗯哼
- Yeah.     - Hmm.
你们知道吗？
You know what?
这星期我已经失去一个假爸爸
I've already lost a fake dad this week.
我想我还没准备好要失去真爸爸
I don't think I'm ready to lose a real one.
菲比 没关系的 今天你跨出一大步
Pheebs, that's okay. You took a big step today.
- 是吗？ - 对
- Yeah?     - Yeah.
有一天当你准备好后 你会跨过灌木丛
Someday, when you're ready, you'll make it past the hedges.
当你那么做 他会很庆幸自己有个这样的女儿
And when you do, he'll be lucky to have you.
你们太棒了
You guys.
抱歉你们来不及去买东西了
Sorry about your shopping.
没关系 我们会想出办法的
Oh, that's okay. We'll figure something out.
我知道你不打算进去
I know you're not going in there...
你觉得我能去跟他借厕所吗？
but do you think it'd be all right if I went in and used his bathroom?
没关系 算了
That's fine, never mind.
很酷 下雪了
Cool, snow!
就跟一大张画布一样
Kind of like a blank canvas.
天啊 真的好热
Ho-ho-ho-holy crap, is it hot in here!
我可以关掉暖气吗？
You mind if I turn the heat down?
我们该早点想到那一点的
We could have used that kind of thinking earlier!
菲比 怎么样？
So, Pheebs, how did it go?
我没办法进去
Oh, ahem, I couldn't go in.
- 甜心 我很遗憾   - 你还好吧？
- Honey, I'm sorry.     - Are you okay?
没事 因为我知道他在那里
Yeah, it's okay, because I know he's there.
现在那就够了
So that's enough for now.
已经过了午夜 祝大家圣诞快乐
Hey, it's after midnight! Merry Christmas, everyone!
对 圣诞快乐
Oh, right! Merry Christmas!
嘿 摩妮卡 开关坏了
The knob was broken...
我就从下面把暖气整个关掉 希望你不介意
so I turned it off from underneath. I hope that's all right.
瑞秋 这是给你的
Rach, these are for you.
雨刷
Wiper blades.
可是我没车
I don't even have a car.
没错 有了这个新汽车芳香剂 你会以为自己真的有车
Ha, ha. No, but with this new-car smell, you'll think you do.
好吧 菲比 轮到你了
Okay, Pheebs, your turn.
马桶座垫纸
Toilet-seat covers.
你们趁我去加油时买的吗？
Is that what you were doing while I was getting gas?
- 嗯哼   - 唔
- Uh-huh.     - Mm-hm.
你们太贴心了
You guys!
给罗斯的礼物
And for Ross...
爱吃甜的家伙
Mr. Sweet Tooth.
你们送我可乐
You got me a cola drink?
还有柠檬口味的
And a lemon-lime!
这太多了 我觉得我该再送你一件毛衣
Well, this is too much. I feel like I should get you another sweater.
最后一位
And last but not least...
在亲热时给你最佳保护
They're ribbed for your pleasure.